

# Mandar Vyas

#### **ABOUT ME**

- +91 9004472048
- A-403, Bldg 89, Jyoti CHS, Tilak Nagar, Mumbai 400089
- mandar.vyas20@gmail.com
- ☐ https://github.com/keeplay20
- https://www.linkedin.co m/in/mandar-vyas-1303b179/

### **PROFILE**

With 8+ experience, I specialize in automating tests for both mobile and web platforms, as well as conducting manual for Linux-based testing operating systems, applications, and mobile apps. I well-versed in methodologies and have a strong tooling mindset, which enables me to achieve higher accuracy and superior quality in my work.

#### SKILLS & TOOLS

Back End

Java

Automation

- Appium
- TestNG

Front End

- HTML, CSS, JS
- React Native

CI / CD

- Ienkins
- Github Actions

Database: **MySql**Version Control: **Git**Defect Tracking: **JIRA** 

Test Management : **Test Rail** Agile Methodologies : **Scrum** 

## WORK EXPERIENCE

#### DREAM11 - SDET 2

Aug 2021 - Present

Responsible for ensuring the front-end quality of features on both Android and iOS platforms.

- Automation of deposits and withdrawal of money by creating **Mock payment framework**.
- Automation of all functional test cases and reducing regression time to 4 hours from 2 days.
- Created Jenkins job to create app and execute automation on both platform and integrated slack messages.
- Mentoring juniors and team mates in their daily chore.
- Tools: JIRA, TestRail, Appium, Slack Bot, Postman, Burp suite, Automation framework using Page Object Model.

## GUPSHUP - SW. QA ENGINEER Feb 2019 - Aug 2021

Responsible for ensuring back-end quality of features including load test.

- Automation of back end components like HTTPSender, SMSSender, Solutions.
- Performance testing using Jmeter and Postman.
- Shell scripts to generate test data for manual testing.
- Mentoring juniors and team mates in their daily chore.
- **Tools**: JIRA, Automation using Keyword driven framework, Postman, Jmeter, MySql.

#### **VXL - SOFTWARE TESTER**

Nov 2016 - Feb 2019

Responsible for Linux based OS (LetOS and Gio6) testing and Web based portal testing using selenium.

- Automation testing of Web application called as Lenovo Terminal Manager using Selenium and TestNG.
- Manual testing of linux based OS called as Gio6/LeTOS developed for thin clients.
- Collaborate with development and product teams to define test plans, identify test cases, and ensure test coverage.
- Mentoring juniors and team mates in their daily chore.

#### **FREELANCING**

Nov 2015 - Nov 2016

## WIPRO - TECH. CONSULTANT

Mar 2014 - Nov 2015

Responsible for installing, configuring and providing support to resolve issues of SharePoint Server.

- Installing, configuring and managing the Microsoft SharePoint Server 2013.
- Provide support to users of EMEA and APAC region while using SharePoint Online.
- Developing custom pages using SharePoint Tools.

## CERTIFICATION

ISTQB - CT-TAE (Test Automation Engineer)

ISTQB - CTFL (Foundation Level)

## **EDUCATION HISTORY**

BE Computers - Pune University Sep 2009 - July 2013

**Grade** - Distinction